loginvsi.com 2011-11-05

# Login Consultants - Specialisten in virtualisatie - Privacy Statement

**LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV Privacy practices on the web highlights**  
**Scope**. This statement applies to LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV Web Sites Worldwide.  

**Personal information**  
In general, you can visit us on the internet without telling us who you are or giving us personal information. There are times when we may need information from you, for instance: to process an order, to correspond, to provide a subscription or in connection with a job application. We may supplement this information to complete a transaction or to provide a better service.

**Uses**

  * To fulfill your requests by us or by others involved in fulfillment. 
  * To contact you for customer satisfaction surveys, market research or in connection with certain transactions. 
  * By LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV and selected organizations for marketing purposes if you have permitted such use. 
  * In an non-identifiable format for analysis (e.g., Clickstream Data) 
  * To develop our business relationship if you represent an LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV Business Partner or Vendor 

**Your choices**

  * When we collect information from you, you may tell us that you do not want it used for further marketing contact and  
we will respect your wishes. 
  * You may also turn off cookies in your browser. 
  * This website uses Google Analytics, and other measurement tools to help analyse how users use the site. These tools use 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Advanced Web Metrics.com.  
We will never (and will not allow any third party) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source, unless you explicity submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

**How to contact us**  
Questions about this statement or  how LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV uses your information may be sent to:   
[****](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy32260%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy32260%20=%20addy32260%20+%20'ibm'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy32260%20+%20'\\'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy32260%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spam%20bots,%20you%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)**[info@loginconsultants.com](mailto:info@loginconsultants.com)** **.**

**LOGIN CONSULTANTS HOLDING BV**  
De Entree 11-13  
1101 BH Amsterdam  
The Netherlands   
+31 20 342 02 80
